http://www.vagardenweek.org/main/privacy-policy

Effective
Date: August 2019The Garden Club of Virginia (GCV) respects your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Statement describes the types of personal information we collect on gcvirginia.org (the “Site”), how we use the information, with whom we share it and the choices available to you regarding our use of the information. We also describe measures we take to protect the security of the information and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.This Privacy Statement applies to the information we collect on the Site.It does not apply to other websites, applications or services provided by GCV or other affiliated entities. In addition, this Privacy Statement does not apply to the offline data collection and use practices of GCV or other affiliated entities.Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section:Information You Provide to UsAutomated Collection of InformationCookies and Web BeaconsHow We Use the Information We ObtainThird-Party Analytics ServicesOnline Tracking and Interest-Based AdvertisingInformation We ShareYour ChoicesHow We Protect Personal InformationLinks to Non-GCV Sites and ServicesUpdates to Our Privacy StatementHow to Contact UsInformation You Provide to UsThe
types of personal information you may provide to us when you visit our Site may include: Contact information (such as name, telephone number, postal address and email address);Payment information, such as credit or debit card number, security code, expiration date and billing address;Purchase history information;Gcvirginia.org login credentials, such as your username, password, and security questions and answers;Automated Collection of InformationWhen you visit our Site, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies, web beacons, web server logs and other technologies. The information we collect in this manner may include your device IP address, unique device identifier, web browser characteristics, device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, clickstream data, and dates and times of website visits.
Cookies and Web BeaconsCookies are files that websites send to your computer to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A web beacon (also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF) links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies or how to restrict or disable certain types of cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of the Site.How We Use the Information We ObtainWe may use the personal information we obtain about you to: Provide our products and services to you;Send you newsletters and other email
communications if you sign up to receive them;Administer your participation in surveys,
contests, promotions or other programs;Process orders and payment transactions;Manage delivery services;Operate, evaluate and improve our
business (including managing the Site, developing new products and services;
enhancing and improving our products and services; managing our communications;
analyzing our products, services and customer base; performing data analytics;
and performing accounting, auditing and other internal functions); andProtect against and prevent fraud, unauthorized
transactions, claims and other liabilities;Comply with and enforce applicable legal
requirements and GCV policies and terms.We also may use the information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection. Third-Party Analytics ServicesWe may use third party analytics services on our Site, such as Google Analytics. The analytics providers that administer these services use technologies such as cookies, web beacons and web server logs to help us analyze your use of the Site. The information collected through these means (including IP address) may be disclosed to these analytics providers, and other relevant third parties who use the information to evaluate use of the Site. To learn more about Google Analytics and how to opt out, please visit https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html or https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en. Online Tracking and Interest-Based AdvertisingOn our Site, we and third parties may collect information about your online activities to provide you with advertising about products and services tailored to your interests. This section of our Privacy Statement provides details and explains how to exercise your choices.  You may see our ads on other websites based on your visits to the Site because we participate in advertising networks.  Ad networks allow us to target our messaging to users considering demographic data, users’ inferred interests and browsing context. These networks track users’ online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs, web beacons and other similar technologies.  The networks use this information to show ads that may be tailored to individuals’ interests, to track users’ browsers or devices across multiple websites, and to build a profile of users’ online browsing activities.  The information our ad networks may collect includes data about users’ visits to websites that participate in the relevant ad networks, such as the pages or ads viewed and the actions taken on the websites.  We and our third-party vendors may collect information about our visitors’ online activities, over time and across third-party websites.  This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.  To learn about how to opt out of interest-based advertising in the U.S., click here.  On your mobile device, your device settings may allow you to prohibit mobile app platforms (such as Apple and Google) from sharing certain information obtained by automated means with app developers such as GCV.Our Site is not designed to respond to “do not track” signals received from browsers.Information We ShareWe do not disclose personal information we obtain about you, except as described in this Privacy Statement.  We may share personal information we collect on the Site at your request.  We may share your personal information with our subsidiaries and affiliates, and with our joint marketing partners, for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement.  We also may share personal information with service providers who perform services on our behalf based on our instructions. We do not authorize these service providers to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements.In addition, we may disclose information about you if required to do so by law or if we believe such action is necessary to comply with legal process. We also reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a merger, acquisition, joint venture, reorganization, divestiture, dissolution or liquidation). Your ChoicesYou may at any time ask us to stop sending you emails or other communications. To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists or submit a request, please contact us as described in the How to Contact Us section below.  You may also update your preferences online through your GCV account.How We Protect Personal InformationWe maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized access, destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure or use.Links to Non-GCV Sites and ServicesFor your convenience and information, our Site may provide links to or plug-ins of non-GCV websites, apps and services that may be operated by companies not affiliated with GCV.  The privacy practices of the relevant third parties, including details on the information they may collect about you, is subject to the privacy statements of these parties, which we strongly suggest you review.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any non-GCV websites, apps or services.Updates to Our Privacy StatementThis Privacy Statement may be updated periodically to reflect changes in our personal information practices. Changes to the Privacy Statement will be posted on this page. For significant changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our website indicating at the top of the Statement when it was most recently updated. How to Contact UsYou can update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists, submit a request or ask us questions about this Privacy Statement by calling us at 804-643-4137. You may also send us an
email using the “Contact Us” section of the Site, or write to:Garden Club of Virginia12 East Franklin StreetRichmond, VA 23219
Announcements
Read "Historic Garden Week -- The Magazine"
"Historic Garden Week – The Magazine" is available at these locations across Virginia
Read About the Garden Club of Virginia's First Century in Virginia Living Magazine
Historic Garden Week in Virginia 2021 Media Release
Historic Garden Week by the Numbers (4 MB PDF)
Garden Club of Virginia at 100 - Steel Magnolias Mark a Milestone
Watch Garden Club of Virginia Member Jeanette Cadwallender Share the Beauty of her Fredericksburg Garden and Design a Floral Arrangement
Media inquiries, general information and logistics:
Karen Ellsworth, Historic Garden Week State Director and Editor of the Guidebook
karen@vagardenweek.org or 804-644-7776, Ext. 21
Historic Garden Week Guidebook Ad Sales:
Terri Lowman, Administrative Coordinator
Terri@vagardenweek.org or 804-644-7776, Ext. 22
© 2020 Historic Garden Week in Virginia & Garden Club of Virginia. All Rights Reserved
